export const Quizlet = [
    {
        "Question": "What is CircleCI primarily used for?",
        "Options": ["Continuous integration and delivery", "Cloud storage", "Social networking", "Video streaming"],
        "Answer": "Continuous integration and delivery"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which file is used to configure CircleCI?",
        "Options": [".circleci/config.yml", ".circleci/config.json", "circleci.yml", "config.yml"],
        "Answer": ".circleci/config.yml"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is a job in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["A collection of steps to perform a task", "A single command", "A configuration file", "A user role"],
        "Answer": "A collection of steps to perform a task"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the purpose of a 'workflow' in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["To define how jobs run and in what order", "To store environment variables", "To manage user permissions", "To host static files"],
        "Answer": "To define how jobs run and in what order"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command is used to trigger a new build in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["circleci build", "circleci start", "circleci trigger", "circleci run"],
        "Answer": "circleci build"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you specify a Docker image for a job in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["Using the docker key in the config file", "In the package.json file", "In the Dockerfile", "Using the circleci.json file"],
        "Answer": "Using the docker key in the config file"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is an 'executor' in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["The environment in which a job runs", "A type of job", "A configuration file", "A command to start a build"],
        "Answer": "The environment in which a job runs"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How can you cache dependencies in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["Using the cache key in the config file", "By storing them in a separate repository", "By using local storage", "By using environment variables"],
        "Answer": "Using the cache key in the config file"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is an 'artifact' in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["Files generated by a job that are stored for later use", "A type of job", "A Docker image", "A configuration file"],
        "Answer": "Files generated by a job that are stored for later use"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you define environment variables in CircleCI?",
        "Options": ["In the CircleCI dashboard or in the config file", "In the package.json file", "In the Dockerfile", "In the index.html file"],
        "Answer": "In the CircleCI dashboard or in the config file"
    }
]
